<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Windows on S4MY9&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://s4my9.github.io/tags/windows/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Windows on S4MY9&#39;s Blog</description>
    <image>
      <title>S4MY9&#39;s Blog</title>
      <url>https://s4my9.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://s4my9.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 11:58:47 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://s4my9.github.io/tags/windows/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>[🎓] Dante HTB Prolab</title>
      <link>https://s4my9.github.io/posts/dante-htb-prolab/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 11:58:47 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s4my9.github.io/posts/dante-htb-prolab/</guid>
      <description>In this post, I will share my experience and tips on the Dante ProLab at HackTheBox. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a beginner looking to get started or a professional looking to improve your skills, these insights will be valuable.
Introduction to the Dante Lab The Dante Lab is an ideal choice for those aiming to prepare for the OSCP exam but want to gain practical experience in a realistic corporate environment before investing in the OSCP (minimum $1600) access.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[📝] Ligolo-ng, pivot/tunnel tool.</title>
      <link>https://s4my9.github.io/posts/ligolo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 11:58:47 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s4my9.github.io/posts/ligolo/</guid>
      <description>Ligolo-ng stands out as a straightforward, lightweight, and high-speed tool specifically designed for penetration testers to create tunnels through a reverse TCP/TLS connection using a tun interface, eliminating the need for SOCKS proxies.
/ / (_)___ _____ / /___ ____ ____ _ / / / / __ `/ __ \/ / __ \______/ __ \/ __ `/ / /___/ / /_/ / /_/ / / /_/ /_____/ / / / /_/ / /_____/_/\__, /\____/_/\____/ /_/ /_/\__, / /____/ /____/ Cheat Sheet Here&amp;rsquo;s a cheat sheet with the most commonly used commands:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[⭐] Files Events Monitor</title>
      <link>https://s4my9.github.io/posts/files-events-monitor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 11:58:47 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s4my9.github.io/posts/files-events-monitor/</guid>
      <description>Are you concerned about the integrity and security of your files? Do you want to keep track of any changes or activities in a specific directory? Introducing Files Events Monitor, a simple yet powerful tool to monitor file system activity and receive real-time alerts via Discord webhook.
Files Events Monitor is a Python-based command-line tool designed to keep a vigilant eye on your specified directory for any file system events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[🎓] EJPTv2</title>
      <link>https://s4my9.github.io/posts/ejptv2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 11:58:47 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://s4my9.github.io/posts/ejptv2/</guid>
      <description>One week ago, I successfuly passed the eLearnSecurity Junior Penetration Tester V2 (eJPTv2) certification exam. In this article, I want to share my insights and thoughts on this certification for those considering a career in cybersecurity.
What is eJPTv2? eJPTv2, short for eLearnSecurity Junior Penetration Tester V2, is a certification program offered by eLearnSecurity. Designed for aspiring cybersecurity professionals, particularly those interested in penetration testing, this certification stands out for its practical approach and comprehensive coverage of essential topics.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
